{
    "id": "1_Education_15",
    "claim": "PIETRO BOSELLI, THE MOST SEXY MASTER IN THE WORLD, WILL GIVE CLASSES IN UNAMMexico. - Big surprise caused by President Enrique Peña Nieto, revealing that he has just closed an agreement with the famous professor of mathematics of the University College of London, Pietro Boselli (which went viral all over the world when he was considered'the sexiest teacher on the planet), so that he could take classes for a semester at the National Autonomous University of Mexico in the area of engineering. EPN mentioned that he decided to reveal that the famous professor would come to Mexico to teach for the purpose of 'making it a gift for the teacher's day ', mentioning that it is already a fact that he will teach at the engineering faculty of UNAM, so the number of women who have taken tickets to enter that career increased by %: 'We decided to hire Boselli to raise the academic level of UNAM, decades ago our university was in the top  of the best in the world, and now it is almost out of the top . We need the people of the world to put their eyes on UNAM so that it will regain the prestige of before. It was my advisor who recommended me to bring Boselli, but I was sharp and told him that we had to test him to prove he was a good teacher, and he deserved to get on the government payroll. Of course we're excited about the stir that caused his hiring, but finally my intention is to increase prestige so it's no use that he's so handsome if he's not good at teaching. In the end we realize he's actually much better prepared than the current teachers so we hired him right away. We found it rather expensive to convince him because he is also a model and we had to pay him double, as a teacher and as a model ', he said. EPN noted that 'many women asked him to teach in some degree such as Communication ', however Pietro is an expert in engineering matters: 'When there was a rumor that we would hire him the girls told us to send him to the bachelor's degree where they were studying, but the teacher is an engineering expert and he had no case to teach him in something that is not his area. In the end, the women decided that they would switch to engineering where they were taught. If they are going to make that decision just because they want to see the teacher closely think about it because Boselli will only be there for a semester, and also will only give classes  days a week, since the others will use them to fulfill their other model work ', said Nieto. I'm sorry.",
    "source": "www.elruinaversal.com",
    "date": "19/05/2017",
    "veracity": 0,
    "claims": [
        {
            "claim": "PIETRO BOSELLI, THE MOST SEXY MASTER IN THE WORLD , WILL GIVE CLASSES IN UNAMMexico .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is PIETRO BOSELLI's nickname?",
                    "answer": "THE MOST SEXY MASTER IN THE WORLD"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the crimes committed by Carlo Alberto BOSELLI?",
                    "score": 0.7017,
                    "answers": "on 19/05/2017|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where is UNAM Mexico located?",
                    "score": 0.6583,
                    "answers": "IN UNAMMexico|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "- Big surprise caused by President Enrique Peña Nieto , revealing that President Enrique Peña Nieto has just closed an agreement with the famous professor of mathematics of the University College of London, Pietro Boselli (which went viral all over THE WORLD when PIETRO BOSELLI, THE MOST SEXY MASTER IN THE WORLD was considered'the sexiest teacher on THE WORLD ), so that PIETRO BOSELLI, THE MOST SEXY MASTER IN THE WORLD could take classes for a semester at UNAMMexico in the area of engineering.",
            "question_answers": [],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why did President Enrique Peña Nieto close an agreement with Pietro Boselli?",
                    "score": 0.9079,
                    "answers": "so that PIETRO BOSELLI , THE MOST SEXY MASTER IN THE WORLD could take classes for a semester in the area of engineering at UNAMMexico|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the agreement between Peña Nieto and Pietro Boselli?",
                    "score": 0.7706,
                    "answers": "classes for a semester in the area of engineering|dobj\tin the area of engineering|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "President Enrique Peña Nieto mentioned that President Enrique Peña Nieto decided to reveal that PIETRO BOSELLI, THE MOST SEXY MASTER IN THE WORLD would come to Mexico to teach for the purpose of 'making it a gift for the teacher's day ', mentioning that it is already a fact that PIETRO BOSELLI, THE MOST SEXY MASTER IN THE WORLD will teach at the engineering faculty of UNAMMexico , so the number of women who have taken tickets to enter that career increased by %: 'We decided to hire PIETRO BOSELLI, THE MOST SEXY MASTER IN THE WORLD to raise the academic level of UNAMMexico , decades ago UNAMMexico was in the top  of the best in THE WORLD , and now UNAMMexico is almost out of the top .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Where will PIETRO BOSELLI teach?",
                    "answer": "UNAMMexico"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many women have been hired to teach at UNAM Mexico?",
                    "score": 0.7908,
                    "answers": "who have taken tickets to enter that career|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Peña Nieto say about PIETRO BOSELLI?",
                    "score": 0.7703,
                    "answers": "President|compound\tPresident|compound\tMOST|advmod\tto teach|advcl\tMOST|advmod\tMOST|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is UNAMMexico's academic level?",
                    "score": 0.7593,
                    "answers": "THE WORLD|pobj\tto Mexico|prep\t's|case\tTHE WORLD|pobj\tTHE WORLD|pobj\tthe top|pobj\t  of the best in THE WORLD|dep\tof the best in THE WORLD|prep\tTHE WORLD|pobj\tnow UNAMMexico is almost out of the top|conj\tthe top|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does it mean to teach a teacher's day?",
                    "score": 0.753,
                    "answers": "the teacher 's day|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the employment rate of PIETRO BOSELLI in the engineering faculty of UNAM Mexico?",
                    "score": 0.7529,
                    "answers": "that PIETRO BOSELLI , THE MOST SEXY MASTER IN THE WORLD will teach at the engineering faculty of UNAMMexico|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "We need the people of the world to put eyes on UNAMMexico so that UNAMMexico will regain the prestige of before.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did elruinaversal.com report that we need the people of the world to put eyes on UNAMMexico?",
                    "answer": "19/05/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is UNAMMexico's prestige?",
                    "score": 0.6978,
                    "answers": "www.elruinaversal.com reported on 19/05/2017 that We need the people of the world to put eyes on UNAMMexico so that UNAMMexico will regain the prestige of before|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is UNAMMexico?",
                    "score": 0.6628,
                    "answers": "www.elruinaversal.com|nsubj\ton 19/05/2017|prep\tthat|mark\tWe|nsubj\tthat We need the people of the world to put eyes on UNAMMexico so that UNAMMexico will regain the prestige of before|ccomp\tthe|det\tthe people of the world|nsubj\tthe|det\tthe world|pobj\tto|aux\tthe people of the world to put eyes on UNAMMexico so that UNAMMexico will regain the prestige of before|ccomp\teyes|dobj\ton UNAMMexico|prep\tso|mark\tthat|mark\twill|aux\tso that UNAMMexico will regain the prestige of before|advcl\tthe|det\tthe prestige of before|dobj\tof before|prep\tbefore|pcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is UNAM Mexico?",
                    "score": 0.6446,
                    "answers": "of the world|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It was my advisor who recommended my to bring PIETRO BOSELLI, THE MOST SEXY MASTER IN THE WORLD , but my was sharp and told my advisor that we had to test PIETRO BOSELLI, THE MOST SEXY MASTER IN THE WORLD to prove PIETRO BOSELLI, THE MOST SEXY MASTER IN THE WORLD was a good teacher, and PIETRO BOSELLI, THE MOST SEXY MASTER IN THE WORLD deserved to get on the government payroll.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who did my advisor recommend that I bring to school?",
                    "answer": "PIETRO BOSELLI, THE MOST SEXY MASTER IN THE WORLD"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What position does PIETRO BOSELLI hold on the government payroll?",
                    "score": 0.8172,
                    "answers": "on the government payroll|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did PIETRO BOSELLI do to prove that he was a good teacher?",
                    "score": 0.7898,
                    "answers": "to prove PIETRO BOSELLI , THE MOST SEXY MASTER IN THE WORLD was a good teacher|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of spying on PIETRO BOSELLI?",
                    "score": 0.7425,
                    "answers": "that we had to test PIETRO BOSELLI , THE MOST SEXY MASTER IN THE WORLD to prove PIETRO BOSELLI , THE MOST SEXY MASTER IN THE WORLD was a good teacher|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the relationship between Duterte and PIETRO BOSELLI?",
                    "score": 0.7341,
                    "answers": "who recommended my to bring PIETRO BOSELLI , THE MOST SEXY MASTER IN THE WORLD|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is PIETRO BOSELLI's role in government payroll?",
                    "score": 0.7221,
                    "answers": "a good teacher|attr"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Of course we're excited about the stir that caused his hiring, but finally my intention is to increase prestige so it's no use that he's so handsome if he's not good at teaching.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the goal of Elruinaversal?",
                    "answer": "increase prestige"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does it mean to be good at teaching?",
                    "score": 0.7901,
                    "answers": "that he 's so handsome if he 's not good at teaching|ccomp\tif he 's not good at teaching|advcl\tgood at teaching|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of hiring teachers?",
                    "score": 0.7869,
                    "answers": "www.elruinaversal.com reported on 19/05/2017 that Of course we 're excited about the stir that caused his hiring , but finally my intention is to increase prestige so it 's no use that he 's so handsome if he 's not good at teaching|ROOT\tthat Of course we 're excited about the stir that caused his hiring , but finally my intention is to increase prestige so it 's no use that he 's so handsome if he 's not good at teaching|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of the stir that caused the hiring of the head of the University of Michigan?",
                    "score": 0.7329,
                    "answers": "excited about the stir that caused his hiring|acomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Scott Walker's position before he was hired?",
                    "score": 0.7183,
                    "answers": "Of|advmod\twe|nsubj\tthe|det\t,|punct\tit|nsubj\tno|det\tnot|neg"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In the end we realize he's actually much better prepared than the current teachers so we hired him right away.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did elruinaversal.com report that they hired him?",
                    "answer": "19/05/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the current teachers prepared for?",
                    "score": 0.805,
                    "answers": "www.elruinaversal.com reported on 19/05/2017 that In the end we realize he 's actually much better prepared than the current teachers so we hired him right away|ROOT\tthat|mark\tthe|det\twe|nsubj\tthat In the end we realize he 's actually much better prepared than the current teachers so we hired him right away|ccomp\the|nsubj\the 's actually much better prepared than the current teachers|ccomp\tactually|advmod\tmuch|advmod\tmuch better|advmod\tmuch better prepared than the current teachers|acomp\tthan the current teachers|prep\tthe|det\tcurrent|amod\tthe current teachers|pobj\tso|cc\twe|nsubj\tright|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the best way to prepare a new teacher?",
                    "score": 0.8047,
                    "answers": "In the end|prep\tthe end|pobj\twe hired him right away|conj\tright away|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who is the current teachers that hired him right away?",
                    "score": 0.7351,
                    "answers": "him|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "We found it rather expensive to convince him because he is also a model and we had to pay him double, as a teacher and as a model ', he said.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What two jobs did Elruinaversal have to pay him double?",
                    "answer": "as a teacher and as a model"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How much did it cost to convince a model to work as a teacher and model?",
                    "score": 0.7741,
                    "answers": "it rather expensive to convince him because he is also a model and we had to pay him double , as a teacher and as a model|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the cost of convincing a model?",
                    "score": 0.6986,
                    "answers": "that We found it rather expensive to convince him because he is also a model and we had to pay him double , as a teacher and as a model|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the man that was convinced he was a model?",
                    "score": 0.604,
                    "answers": "to convince him|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between a model and a model?",
                    "score": 0.5995,
                    "answers": "www.elruinaversal.com reported on 19/05/2017 that We found it rather expensive to convince him because he is also a model and we had to pay him double , as a teacher and as a model|ccomp\ton 19/05/2017|prep\tthat|mark\tit|nsubj\trather|advmod\tto|aux\tbecause he is also a model and we had to pay him double , as a teacher and as a model|advcl\talso|advmod\ta|det\ta model|attr\tand|cc\tto|aux\tdouble|advmod\t,|punct\ta|det\tand|cc\tas a model|conj\ta|det\ta model|pobj\t'|punct\t,|punct\twww.elruinaversal.com reported on 19/05/2017 that We found it rather expensive to convince him because he is also a model and we had to pay him double , as a teacher and as a model ' , he said|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "EPN noted that 'many women asked him to teach in some degree such as Communication ', however Pietro is an expert in engineering matters: 'When there was a rumor that we would hire him the girls told us to send him to the bachelor's degree where they were studying, but the teacher is an engineering expert and he had no case to teach him in something that is not his area.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What degree did many women ask Pietro to teach?",
                    "answer": "Communication"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Did EPN hire Pietro to teach?",
                    "score": 0.8247,
                    "answers": "to teach in some degree such as Communication|xcomp\tsome degree such as Communication|pobj\tthat we would hire him|acl\tin something that is not his area|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Where did Pietro get his bachelor's degree?",
                    "score": 0.7786,
                    "answers": "to the bachelor 's degree where they were studying|prep\tthe bachelor 's degree where they were studying|pobj\twhere|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did EPN say about Pietro's bachelor's degree?",
                    "score": 0.7099,
                    "answers": "the bachelor 's|poss"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did the girls tell the girls about Pietro?",
                    "score": 0.705,
                    "answers": "no case to teach him in something that is not his area|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many women asked for Pietro to teach?",
                    "score": 0.6968,
                    "answers": "many women|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In the end, the women decided that they would switch to engineering where they were taught.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did Elruinaversal report that the women decided to switch to engineering?",
                    "answer": "19/05/2017"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Why did the women decide to switch to engineering?",
                    "score": 0.8707,
                    "answers": "that In the end , the women decided that they would switch to engineering where they were taught|ccomp\tthat they would switch to engineering where they were taught|ccomp\tto engineering where they were taught|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many women decided to switch to engineering where they were taught?",
                    "score": 0.7976,
                    "answers": "the women|nsubj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "If they are going to make that decision just because they want to see the teacher closely think about it because Boselli will only be there for a semester, and also will only give classes  days a week, since the others will use them to fulfill their other model work ', said Nieto.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Why will the other teachers use classes days a week?",
                    "answer": "to fulfill their other model work"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many days a week does it take to fulfill a student's other model work?",
                    "score": 0.6435,
                    "answers": "  days a week , since the others will use them to fulfill their other model work|dep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does it mean to make a decision?",
                    "score": 0.6144,
                    "answers": "If they are going to make that decision just because they want to see the teacher closely|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between Boselli and a teacher?",
                    "score": 0.5665,
                    "answers": "that If they are going to make that decision just because they want to see the teacher closely think about it because Boselli will only be there for a semester , and also will only give classes|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}